<Database>
	<!-- Plastic Surgery Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_CRP_SLEEPYPL_SYMPTOMS">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	<!-- Plastic Surgery Mod -->
	<!-- CRP Export (Everything below will be exported to CRP after release) -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_SEROMA</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Seroma</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_SEROMA_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>A seroma is a collection of fluid that builds up under the surface of your skin. Seromas may develop after a surgical procedure, most often at the site of the surgical incision or where tissue was removed. The seroma may take a few weeks to absorb on its own. Letting a seroma absorb on its own is the best way to heal naturally as long as no complications arise.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_POSTOP_PAIN</LocID>                               
		<Text>Post-Operative Pain</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_POSTOP_PAIN_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Postoperative pain is an anticipated and temporary increase in background pain that usually occurs following surgery. Postoperative pain remains a significant problem for patients and a challenge for anesthesiologists and acute pain medicine specialists. Despite advancements in the last two decades with increased use of multimodal analgesic regimens, advancements in regional anesthesia, and use of continuous analgesic infusions postoperatively, certain subgroups of patients will go on to develop chronic postoperative pain. Poorly managed postoperative pain can lead to complications and prolonged rehabilitation.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_M_SCAR_TISSUE</LocID>                               
		<Text>Minor Scar Tissue</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_M_SCAR_TISSUE_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>A scar is a mark that is left on the skin after a wound or an injury to the surface of the skin has healed. The formation of scars or scar tissue is a normal part of the healing process, and occurs when the skin is cut due to injury or surgery. The growth of scar tissue is influenced by many factors, these include: The severity of the original injury. The size, depth and location of the wound on the body.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_MRSA_INFECTION</LocID>                               
		<Text>Resistant S. Aureus Infection</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_MRSA_INFECTION_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) infection is caused by a type of staph bacteria that's become resistant to many of the antibiotics used to treat ordinary staph infections. These can quickly turn into deep, painful abscesses that require surgical draining. Sometimes the bacteria remain confined to the skin. But they can also burrow deep into the body, causing potentially life-threatening infections in bones, joints, surgical wounds, the bloodstream, heart valves and lungs.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_PULMONARY_EMBOLISM</LocID>                               
		<Text>Pulmonary Embolism</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_PULMONARY_EMBOLISM_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Pulmonary embolism (PE) is a blockage of an artery in the lungs by a substance that has moved from elsewhere in the body through the bloodstream (embolism). Most times, a pulmonary embolism is caused by blood clots that travel from the legs, or rarely, other parts of the body (deep vein thrombosis or DVT). Surgery increases a patient's risk for pulmonary embolism. \n\nTreatment Requirements: Cardiology or ICU dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LI_LOCALPOISIONING</LocID>                               
		<Text>Local Anaesthetic Poisoning</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LI_LOCALPOISIONING_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Local anaesthetic toxicity generally occurs as a result of therapeutic error. Situations leading to toxicity include inadvertent venous or arterial injection as well as too high a dose of ingested or topically administered local anaesthetic-containing preparations. The CNS is more sensitive to the effects of local anesthetics than the cardiac system and will generally manifest signs/symptoms of toxicity first.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LI_BAGGY_SKIN</LocID>                               
		<Text>Asymmetric or ‘Baggy’ Skin Surface</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LI_BAGGY_SKIN_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>When fat is removed from under the skin, some patients believe that their skin will shrink to fit their smoother, more toned body. However, this is not always the case, especially in the areas where the skin is significantly damaged. This is most common in the stomach and gluteal area, though it can occur all over the body. If skin has been stretched over fat deposits for a long period of time, it will may not tighten or shrink back when the fat deposits are no longer there. Any area that has stretch marks, for example, is unlikely to quickly tighten after liposuction. Excess and sagging skin is the most common cause for dimpling after liposuction.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_WOUND_INFECTION2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Wound Infection</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_WOUND_INFECTION2_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>A wound infection occurs when germs, such as bacteria, grow within the damaged skin of a wound.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_RAPID_BLINKING</LocID>                               
		<Text>Excessive Blinking</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_RAPID_BLINKING_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Blinking is a reflex, which means your body does it automatically. You can also make yourself blink when you want to. Excessive blinking is when you blink more than you want to. Excessive blinking is caused by over-stimulation of the blinking reflex. This is most commonly due to a foreign body in the eye. This can be as simple as an ingrown eyelash rubbing against the front of the eyeball. Thus anything which causes a corneal abrasion causes excessive blinking and watering in an attempt to wash out the foreign body. Excessive blinking may also be caused by allergic reactions causing watering, itching and roughening of the conjunctiva. There are other also many other disease states associated with excessive blinking. Treatment for excessive blinking depends on the underlying cause.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LAZY_EYE</LocID>                               
		<Text>Amblyopia (Lazy Eye)</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LAZY_EYE_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Amblyopia is a vision development disorder in which an eye fails to achieve normal visual acuity, even with prescription eyeglasses or contact lenses. Also called lazy eye, amblyopia begins during infancy and early childhood. In most cases, only one eye is affected.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_EYE_DIPLOPIA</LocID>                               
		<Text>Diplopia (Double Vision)</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_EYE_DIPLOPIA_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Diplopia, also known as Double Vision, is the simultaneous perception of two images of a single object that may be displaced horizontally, vertically, diagonally (i.e., both vertically and horizontally), or rotationally in relation to each other.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_EYE_CONJU_SCAR</LocID>                               
		<Text>Conjunctival Scarring</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_EYE_CONJU_SCAR_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Conjunctival scaring can be a persistent problem after surgery. Instead of returning to the typical translucent white appearance, the conjunctiva can remain chronically hyperemic and pink. Many conditions can cause the conjunctiva, the thin transparent membrane that covers the white of the eye and the underside of the eyelids, to become scarred. Scarring damages the conjunctiva and prevents it retaining the protective mucous layer, which helps tears adhere to the surface.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_FOLLICULITIS</LocID>                               
		<Text>Folliculitis</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_FOLLICULITIS_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Folliculitis is a common skin condition in which hair follicles become inflamed. It's usually caused by a bacterial or fungal infection. At first it may look like small red bumps or white-headed pimples around hair follicles — the tiny pockets from which each hair grows.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_MILD_AR</LocID>                               
		<Text>Mild Allergic Reaction</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_MILD_AR_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient has had a mild allergic reaction during or after the surgery. This may be a reaction to certain anaesthetic drugs used, environmental conditions, other types of drugs or materials used during surgery or even the wound dressings.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_THPAFA</LocID>                               
		<Text>Thickening of the Palmar Fascia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_THPAFA_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The palmar fascia is a triangular structure in the palm of the hand based distally. When thickened it becomes tight and shortened, contracting the fingers inwards toward the palm.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_H_BENT_DIGIT</LocID>                               
		<Text>Bent Digit of the Hand</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_H_BENT_DIGIT_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient has presented with a finger that is bent inwards on their hand and while they still have motor control of the finger the patient is unable to correct the bending themselves.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_H_THICKCORD</LocID>                               
		<Text>Prominent Cord</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_H_THICKCORD_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient has a hardened and thick muscle/tissue cord on their hand.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_DIMPLES</LocID>                               
		<Text>Dimpling of the Skin</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_DIMPLES_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient's skin has a dimpled appearance, similar to the surface structure of an orange peel or golf ball.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_OOST</LocID>                               
		<Text>Overgrowth of Scar Tissue</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_OOST_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Overgrowth of scar tissue occurs when too much collagen is produced at the site of the wound. The scar keeps growing, even after the wound has healed.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING1</LocID>                               
		<Text>Very Light Bleeding</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING1_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient is bleeding very lightly, there is typically no change in vital signs and fluid resuscitation is not usually necessary. Bleeding like this will usually stop on its own.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Light Bleeding</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING2_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient is bleeding lightly, there is typically no change in vital signs and fluid resuscitation is not usually necessary. Stopping the bleeding may be necessary to prevent further complications.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING3</LocID>                               
		<Text>Moderate Bleeding</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING3_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient is bleeding somewhat heavily, invention is necessary to prevent hypovolemic shock.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING4</LocID>                               
		<Text>Severe Bleeding</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING4_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient is bleeding heavily, invention is critical to prevent hypovolemic shock.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING5</LocID>                               
		<Text>Catastrophic Bleeding</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEEDING5_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>The patient is bleeding heavily, immediate intervention is needed to save the patient's life.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>