<Database>
	<!-- CRP Mod with Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_CRP_SLEEPY_TREATMENTS">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_IMIQUIMOD_CREAM</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Imiquimod Cream</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_IMIQUIMOD_CREAM_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Imiquimod is a prescription cream that acts as an immune response modifier that is used to treat superficial basal cell carcinoma and actinic keratosis. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_PHOTODYNAMIC_THERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Photodynamic Therapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_PHOTODYNAMIC_THERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Photodynamic therapy is a treatment that uses certain drugs called photosensitizing agents, along with a special light, to kill cancer cells. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_DOCTORS_ADVICE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Oncology Patient Advice</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_DOCTORS_ADVICE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>The doctor gives the patient advice on how to deal with their situation, helps the patient better understand their options such as palliative care and does whatever they can to ensure the patient has the best quality of life possible during this time. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_TARGETED_THERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Targeted Therapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_TARGETED_THERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Targeted therapies are drugs or other substances that block the growth and spread of cancer by interfering with specific molecules. Targeted therapies differ from standard chemotherapy because they are designed to act on specific molecular targets and attack cancer cells without harming healthy cells. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_CHEMOTHERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Chemotherapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_CHEMOTHERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Chemotherapy is a type of cancer treatment that uses one or more anti-cancer drugs as part of a standardized chemotherapy regimen. Chemotherapy may be given with a curative intent, or it may aim to prolong life or to reduce symptoms. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_IMMUNOTHERAPY_DRUGS</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Immunotherapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_IMMUNOTHERAPY_DRUGS_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Immunotherapy is a type of cancer treatment which assists the body's immune system to fight cancer. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_EPIPEN</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Epinephrine Autoinjector</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_EPIPEN_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>An epinephrine autoinjector is a medical device for injecting a measured dose or doses of epinephrine by means of autoinjector technology. It is most often used for the treatment of anaphylaxis. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_MITOTANE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Mitotane</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_MITOTANE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Mitotane, sold under the brand name Lysodren, is a steroidogenesis inhibitor and cytostatic antineoplastic medication which is used in the treatment of adrenocortical carcinoma and Cushing's syndrome. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_SPIRONOLACTONE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Spironolactone</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_SPIRONOLACTONE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Spironolactone is a potassium-sparing diuretic (water pill) that prevents your body from absorbing too much salt and keeps your potassium levels from getting too low. Spironolactone is used to treat heart failure, high blood pressure (hypertension), or hypokalemia (low potassium levels in the blood). \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_OCTREOTIDE_INJECTION</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Octreotide Injection</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_OCTREOTIDE_INJECTION_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Octreotide is used for the treatment of growth hormone producing tumors (acromegaly and gigantism) and can assist in stabilising a patient suffering from a carcinoid crisis. \n\nRequired room: Any office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>     
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_ACTIVE_MONITOR</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Active Monitoring</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_ACTIVE_MONITOR_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Active monitoring is when the oncologist recommends no treatment but monitors the patient's health with regular check-ups and blood tests. This is sometimes called “careful monitoring” or “watch and wait”. \n\nRequired room: Any Oncology office</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>     
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_HYPER_CVAD</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Intensive Hyper-CVAD Therapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_HYPER_CVAD_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>The term 'hyper' refers to the hyperfractionated nature of the chemotherapy, which is given in smaller doses, more frequently, to minimize side effects. 'CVAD' is the acronym of the drugs used in course A: cyclophosphamide, vincristine, doxorubicin (also known by its trade name, Adriamycin), and dexamethasone. Short-term intensive therapies show improved results. \n\nRequired room: High Priority Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_G_CSF</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>G-CSF Drugs</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_G_CSF_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Granulocyte-colony stimulating factors drugs, also known as colony-stimulating factor 3, is a glycoprotein that stimulates the bone marrow to produce granulocytes and stem cells and release them into the bloodstream. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_METHOTREXATE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Methotrexate IV</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_METHOTREXATE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Methotrexate, formerly known as amethopterin, is a chemotherapy agent and immune system suppressant. It is used to treat cancer, autoimmune diseases, ectopic pregnancy, and for medical abortions. Types of cancers it is used for include breast cancer, leukemia, lung cancer, lymphoma, and osteosarcoma. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_ALEMTUZUMAB</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Alemtuzumab IV</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_ALEMTUZUMAB_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Alemtuzumab is a medication used to treat chronic lymphocytic leukemia and multiple sclerosis. In CLL, Alemtuzumab has been used as both a first line and second line treatment. In MS it is generally only recommended if other treatments have not worked. It is given by injection into a vein. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_BRAF_INH</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>BRAF Inhibitors</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_BRAF_INH_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>BRAF Inhibitors help block the BRAF-V600E gene mutation. In clinical trials, B-Raf increased metastatic melanoma patient chance of survival. In spite of the drug's high efficacy, 20% of tumors still develop resistance to the treatment. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_TAMOXIFEN</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Tamoxifen</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_TAMOXIFEN_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Tamoxifen is a hormone therapy for breast cancer in both women and men. It lowers the risk of early breast cancer coming back (recurring) after surgery or developing in the other breast. It can also control advanced breast cancer for some time. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_HYPERSALINE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Hypertonic Saline</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_HYPERSALINE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Hyperosmolar therapy with hypertonic saline or mannitol can rapidly reduce intracranial pressure, possibly saving lives and brain cells. Hypertonic saline is effective because it does not cross the blood-brain barrier (much), and thereby draws cerebrospinal fluid out of the cranium and fluid out of the injured brain, reducing pressure and further injury. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_INCISION_AND_DRAINAGE</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Incision and drainage</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_INCISION_AND_DRAINAGE_DESC</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Incision and drainage and clinical lancing are minor surgical procedures to release fuild or pressure built up under the skin. \n\nRequired room: Oncology Diagnostic Unit / Oncology Doctor's Office / ICU / Observation Room</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_ESTRADIOL_CREAM</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Estradiol Cream</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_ESTRADIOL_CREAM_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Estradiol cream is a preparation of estrogen, a female hormone, for topical application to the vaginal area used to treat certain symptoms of menopause such as dryness, burning, and itching of the vaginal area and urgency or irritation with urination. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_HORMONE_THERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Hormone Therapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_HORMONE_THERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Hormone therapy or hormonal therapy is the use of hormones in medical treatment. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_RCHOP</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>R-CHOP Chemotherapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_RCHOP_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>R-CHOP is a combination treatment used to treat non-Hodgkin lymphoma (NHL). R-CHOP includes five chemotherapy drugs: rituximab (Rituxan) cyclophosphamide. doxorubicin hydrochloride, vincristine and prednisolone. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_RITUXIMAB</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Rituximab</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_RITUXIMAB_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Rituximab, sold under the brand name Rituxan among others, is a medication used to treat certain autoimmune diseases and types of cancer. Rituximab is a chimeric monoclonal antibody against the protein CD20, which is primarily found on the surface of immune system B cells. When it binds to this protein it triggers cell death. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_GEMCITABINE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Gemcitabine</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_GEMCITABINE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Gemcitabine, sold under the brand name Gemzar, among others, is a chemotherapy medication used to treat a number of types of cancer. These cancers include breast cancer, ovarian cancer, non-small cell lung cancer, pancreatic cancer, and bladder cancer. It is given by slow injection into a vein. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_POCT</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>POC Combination Treatment</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_POCT_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Pamidronate and Octreotide Combination Treatment. Isolated reports suggest that pamidronate and octreotide may help in relieving bone pain in some cases and assist in the treatment of hypertrophic pulmonary osteoarthropathy (HPOA). Treatment of the underlying problem is necessary to resolve the issue.  \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_FEP</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>FEP Combination Treatment</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_FEP_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>5-Fluorouracil (5-FU), Cisplatin, and Etoposide (FEP) Combination Treatment. Chemotherapy has relatively poor curative efficacy in certain cancers such as Signet Ring Cell Carcinoma (SRCC) and patients and overall survival rates are lower compared to patients with more typical cancer pathology. These cancers are usually diagnosed during the late stages of the disease, so the tumors generally spread more aggressively than non-signet cancers, making treatment challenging but most active regimens include 5-Fluorouracil (5-FU), Cisplatin, and/or Etoposide. FEP combination chemotherapy seems to be an effective treatment regimen for gastric cancer as salvage chemotherapy. \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_AMMONUL</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Ammonul</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_AMMONUL_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Ammonul (sodium benzoate and sodium phenylacetate combination) is used to treat a condition caused by too much ammonia in the blood (hyperammonemia). \n\nRequired room: Regular Hospitalisation at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_LACTULOSE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Lactulose</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_LACTULOSE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Lactulose is a prescription drug used by mouth or rectally to treat or prevent complications of liver disease (hepatic encephalopathy). It does not cure the problem, but may help to improve mental status. Lactulose is a colonic acidifier that works by decreasing the amount of ammonia in the blood. \n\nRequired room: Any office.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_IMMUNOSUS_DRUGS</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Immunosuppressive Drugs</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_CRP_IMMUNOSUS_DRUGS_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Immunosuppressant drugs are a class of drugs that suppress, or reduce, the strength of the body’s immune system. Some of these drugs are used to make the body less likely to reject a transplanted organ, such as a liver, heart, or kidney. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Oncology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<!-- ### ### -->
	<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.15.0.0 Added Below ######################################## -->
	<!-- ### ### -->
	
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
